

Sebastian Ibañez

Front-end Developer

Contacto

sebaasibanez@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/sebastian-ibanez/

Skills

Angular

React

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Java

Languages

Spanish

English

Portuguese

Japanese

Profile

I consider myself a person capable of always looking for the most appropriate solutions to the situation. Front end developer with more than 5 years of experience, mainly focused on clear and precise code building to meet the customer objectives and needs.

Education

Degree in computer science

2018 – Actualidad

National University of La Plata

Argentina Programa (First stage)

2021 - 2021

Argentina Programa - Ministry of Productive Performance

Argentina Programa (Second stage)

2022 - 2022

Argentina Programa - Ministry of Productive Performance

Experiences

Front-End Developer

2018 - 2019

Hotel Inkawasi - Developer in charge of maintaining the ecommerce system for hotel reservations and orders.

FreeLancer

2018 – 2022

Design and development of web projects, building backend for small applications with NodeJS, SpringBoot, and PHP. Maintenance and improvement of websites and applications. SEO optimization.